{
  "questions":
  [
    {
      "question": "He fell from grace, when he flew too close to the sun",
      "answers": [
        "Achilles",
        "Icarus",
        "Morpheus",
        "Daedalus"
      ],
      "answerindex": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Odin and the rest of norse gods are fated to perish in this catoclysmic event",
      "answers": [
        "Apocalypse",
        "Armageddon",
        "Jormungand",
        "Ragnarok"
      ],
      "answerindex": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "His cleaning of the stables, was quite a feat",
      "answers": [
        "Samson",
        "Mars",
        "Hercules",
        "Aaron"
      ],
      "answerindex": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "This deity also has a falcon-head, but was God of kings and the sky",
      "answers": [
        "Ra",
        "Horus",
        "Hedwig",
        "Icarus"
      ],
      "answerindex": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "This messenger of the Gods is known by the Romans as",
      "answers": [
        "Apollo",
        "Pluto",
        "Mercury",
        "Hermes"
      ],
      "answerindex": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "He wasn't as happy as you might think, turning all he touched into gold",
      "answers": [
        "Midas",
        "Minerva",
        "Herod",
        "Mars"
      ],
      "answerindex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "He used a shiny mirrored shield to slay the Gorgon Medusa",
      "answers": [
        "Percy",
        "Perseus",
        "Polynices",
        "Hephaestus"
      ],
      "answerindex": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "This enourmous wolf had to be chained up, lest his rampaging destroy the world",
      "answers": [
        "Remus",
        "Grendel",
        "Romulus",
        "Fenrir"
      ],
      "answerindex": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "When he was dipped in the river Styx, his mother may have missed a spot",
      "answers": [
        "Hercules",
        "Achilles",
        "Goliath",
        "Paris"
      ],
      "answerindex": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Nothing gets past him, as divine sentry of Asgard",
      "answers": [
        "Heimdall",
        "Thor",
        "Odin",
        "Methuselah"
      ],
      "answerindex": 0
    }
  ]
}